reliancenipponlife.com 2019-06-30

# Privacy Policy

At Reliance Nippon Life Insurance, we are committed to protect and maintain the confidentiality of any information relating to our customer.

The information about your domain name, date and time of access to the website, internet address which linked you to our website and the pages that you visited collected by us, would be kept confidential and would be used for the following purposes only:

  * To meet legal requirements (if any)
  * To protect and defend Reliance Nippon Life Insurance or its Affiliates' rights, interests or property
  * To analyse the usage pattern of the site or to get statistics on the number of visitors to the site
  * For processing and assessment of your application/claims and/or to perform or provide necessary service or assistance under the insurance contract.

RNLIC shall disclose and/or transfer your sensitive personal information or other information collected, stored, processed by us to third parties in case it is necessary for providing services to you and/or if you have consented to the same. This may also include sharing of information with them in order for them to understand our environment and consequently, provide you with better services. While sharing your sensitive personal information with third parties, adequate measures will be taken by the company to ensure that reasonable security practices are followed by the third parties as provided under the IT Act.

In case of any complaints in respect of unauthorised access to sensitive customer information or unauthorised usage of such computer resource of the company by any person in violation of rule 3 of Information Technology (Intermediaries guidelines) Rules, 2011, you can address the complaint to Mr. Srinivasan Iyengar, Chief Operating Officer, at [srinivasan.iyengar@relianceada.com](mailto:%20srinivasan.iyengar@relianceada.com). The complaint can also be in writing duly signed by the complainant and shall state clearly the name and address of the complainant, the name of the branch/ service provider, the fact giving rise to complaint supported by documents, if any and the nature and extent of the loss caused to the complainant and the relief sought, if any. We assure you that such complaints will be redressed in a speedy manner, though not exceeding one month in any case.

RNLIC may share your personal information, including sensitive data, without your prior consent to government agencies mandated under the law, to obtain such information for purposes of verification of identity, prevention, detection and investigation of cyber incidents and fraud, prosecution and punishment of offences, or where such disclosure is necessary as per legal and regulatory requirements.

Sensitive data/ information defined herein shall also include personal information as defined under the IT Act.

Reliance Nippon Life Insurance will not be responsible in any manner for any direct or indirect damages that may arise out of the use of this website.

Reliance Nippon Life Insurance has the right to change any part of the said content on the website at any time at its sole discretion.
